<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AllotaWatch</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Allotawatch</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">allotawatch - the time budgeting app</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_task2">NewTaskActivity2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings2">SettingsActivity2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_info">ActivityInfo</string>
    <string name="info_title">Help</string>
    <string name="section_content_about">
        About\n\n
        It’s a simple timer app that allows you to allocate the time in your working day for tasks
        that you need to get done\n
        It was inspired by an article from waitbutwhy.com that highlights how limited our time is\n
        It allows you to switch between tasks freely and still be sure you are properly investing
        the amount of time that you have.\n
        While working on long term projects or goals have you ever felt bogged down or tired from
        working on the same thing for too long? Because if you are like me, you get bored of one
        thing very easily. When you get bored, switch to something else productive instead of procrastinating.
        It’s a good app for multitaskers.\n
        Knowing how much time you’ve spent allows you to match it to how much work you’ve done forcing
        you to get a move on if needed.\n
        Its best to back away for a while and take a break, but for how long? This app allows you to
        easily switch between them when you need to refresh your mind and body and work on something
        different for a while. Switching like this allows you to have a flexible and reactive schedule
        as opposed to a rigid one.\n
        You will also be able to see how much time has passed since your last break and recommends taking
        one every hour. It also warns you when you’ve been taking too long a break.\n
        This app should allow you to accomplish more in a day to spend your time more effectively.\n
        The app is useful for long term goals or short-term workouts. \n
        You can create a plan for your day and easily budget the time you have available between the
        tasks that you must do.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_getstarted_p1">
        Get Started\n\n
        1. Add new tasks by clicking on the floating action button.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_getstarted_p2">
        2. Specify a name and use the sliders to set how much time you need to spend on this task.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_getstarted_p3">
        3. You can cancel your input or create the task.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_getstarted_p4">
        4. The name must be unique, if not, it will replace the time of the existing task.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_getstarted_p5">
        5. Click the play button to start or stop the tracking.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_getstarted_p6">
        6. Use swipe gestures on the home screen to control the time tracker.\n
        \ta. Left or right switches the task\n
        \tb. Down puts you on break.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_getstarted_p7">
        7. You can also control the task from the notification icon.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_getstarted_p8">
        8. You can see information about the time tracking below the timer it shows.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_actions_p1">
        Actions\n\n
        - Switching tasks\n
        \tSwipe left or right at the home screen.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_actions_p2">
        - Taking a break\n
        \tSwipe down at the home screen.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_actions_p3">
        - Creating a task\n
        \tClick the floating action button at the home screen.\n
	    \tClicking it at the budgeting page will add it to the list currently displayed.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_actions_p4">
        - Quick alarm\n
        \tYou can set an alarm that will run parallel to the main timer. The ringing bell icon indicates
        that an alarm is already set.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_actions_p5">
        - Save lists\n
        \tSwipe up at the home screen. Then press the save button. You can cycle through the lists by
        swiping up or pressing the next button.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_actions_p6">
        - Start or stop the timer\n
        \tStart or stop time tracking, stopping will also stop the quick alarm. If you only need an
        alarm its recommended that you create a new task to do so.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_actions_p7">
        - Delete task\n
        \tClicking the close button at a task will do this. You can also do this at the budgeting page.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_actions_p8">
        - Load page\n
        \tUse the list that is currently displayed for tracking.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_actions_p9">
        - New page\n
        \tCreates a new list but deletes the one currently in use.\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_budget">
        Budget time\n\n
        Swipe up to see lists of tasks. For each list you can allocate how much time you want to spend
        on those tasks at the bottom.\n
        You allocate how much time per day then how many days you want to spend. The max per day is 16
        hours.\n
        Then you can ration out that time between the tasks in the list using the sliders. The time
        allocated to that task is on the left margin adjacent it. Sliders at the same position will
        have time divided equally.\n
        It shows how much break time is recommended for the time spent working in brackets. It
        recommends 10 minutes per work hour and will be tracked when switching to break.\n\n
        For example.\n
        If I\n
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_contact">
        Contact\n\n
        edsoft@gmail.com\n\n\n
        message\n\n\n
        your contact email
    </string>
    <string name="section_content_bugs">
        Report bugs\n\n
        edsoft@gmail.com\n\n\n
        feature name\n\n\n
        environment\n\n\n
        steps to reproduce\n\n\n
        expected result\n\n\n
        actual result\n\n\n
        visual proof (screenshots, videos)\n\n\n
        additional notes\n\n\n
        your contact email
    </string>
</resources>
